new York, NY

☐ lunina.anastasiya@gmail.com linktps://www.linkedin.com/in/anastasia-lunina/ lunina/ lunina/

Medium blog: https://medium.com/@lunina.anastasiya Portfolio: https://anastasia-codes.netlify.app/

(631)406-3798

FULL STACK SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

Experienced Full Stack Web Developer. Curious, easily adaptable, attentive to details, using my passion and skills to create exceptional products. I love to learn, explore and think. Coding is giving me a rewarding feeling of a never-ending puzzle, which I enjoy solving every day. I've always been a mix of a creative person and a logical one, software development is the perfect field for combining both.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Programming : Python, Django, Docker, SQL, JavaScript, React, Typescript, HTML, CSS, Bootsrtap

Databases : Oracle, MySQL, PostgreSQL

Version Control : Git/GitHub

Platforms : Windows, Mac, UNIX/LINUX

Testing Tools : Postman

Other : AutoCAD, SolidWorks, Adobe, Figma, Jira/Xray

WORK EXPERIENCE

Web Developer, Self-employed

Jan 2021 - Present

- Met with the prospective clients to gather specifications for new or existing websites
- Designed, coded quality websites using HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, React, Postgresql, Python
- Prepared multiple designs and wireframes for clients' approval before proceeding with development
- · Conducted testing of websites across all major browsers to ensure quality and consistency throughout
- Redesigned website to a clean modern minimalistic design with complete mobile responsiveness.

Software QA Engineer, Q-Softpro, Inc., Remote

Jun 2020 - Present

- Tested Web-based applications developed by the company's clients
- Worked with Product Owner and Development Team to ensure all requirements were met
- · Developed and executed test cases, using Xray /Jira to monitor test executions, and capture results
- Executed Smoke and Regression testing for every new build
- Performed API testing based on Swagger, created and automated collections using JavaScript and ran them using Postman
- Developed and executed SQL queries to validate frontend and backend data integrity (MySQL, PostgreSQL)
- Worked in Agile/ Scrum environment, actively participated in Stand-Up meetings, Sprint Planning meetings, and Sprint Retrospective meetings, provided input on the application functionality and testing process improvement recommendations

Drafting Manager, ESF Inc., New York, NY

Sep 2016 - Mar 2020

- Followed specifications and calculations to create drawings for various projects
- Visited sites, making necessary measurements for future drawings
- Communicated with architects and engineers, and incorporated knowledge gained into drawings
- Ensured final designs were compliant with building regulations
- Identified and communicating potential design problems to the project team
- Prepared both rough sketches and detailed work using CAD systems

PROJECTS

Vkinder. Backend App coded in Python.

Chat-bot interacting with database of social media network vk.com. Bot collecting the user's info by getting the user's ID through API and based on that offers three images of people, who matches the user's interests, along with person's info, built as a dialogue with the user. User can decline or add to match to favorites. All data is writes to a database. User can look at favorites list or at black list at any time.

Technologies used: Python, Postgresql, Sqlalchemy, API, requests library

Link to the project: GitHub

Backup to cloud. Backend App coded in Python.

Program which copies photos from vk.com to cloud storage on Yandex.disc. Program chooses largest image, renames image based on likes quantity, creates folder on Yandex disc and copies images to created folder.

<u>Technologies used:</u> Python, API, requests library

Link to the project: GitHub

JS_Track_Finance_App. Frontend App coded in JavaScript using classes and API.

JavaScript app. User can register, login, logout, create personal app account. User is able to track several bank accounts. User can add or delete new transaction, see the list of all transactions for each bank account.

<u>Technologies used:</u> JavaScript <u>Link to the project: GitHub</u>

JS_Food_App. Frontend App coded in JavaScript.

App for healthy food services. API, Slider, calculator, modal, countdown

<u>Technologies used:</u> JavaScript <u>Link to the project:</u> <u>GitHub</u>

EDUCATION

Bachelor's Degree in Economics, Southern Federal University, Rostov, Russia